gapoon.com 2016-06-21

# Privacy Policy - Gapoon

## Select your desired service

#### or

## Click here to explore current page

Welcome to the web site of Gapoon.com operated by Gapoon and has been created to provide information about our company and the services. By visiting this website, calling our telephone numbers or using our services (collectively referred as ‘Services’) through mediums like telephone, SMS and WAP or any other medium in which Gapoon may provide services you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

When you interact with us through the Services, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, which typically includes : 

  * Name
  * Telephone Number
  * Email Address
  * Home Address
  * Information about your home which you give us
  * Your IP address and any other personal information which you give us in connection with the Services.

This Personal Information is used for three general purposes: to customize the content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain services, and to contact you about our services. Unless stated otherwise explicitly, this Policy applies to Personal Information as disclosed on the website. 

Personal Information will be kept confidential and will be used for our research, marketing, and strategic client analysis and other internal business purposes only. We do not sell or rent Personal Information except that in case you are a customer of our search services through the website, your Personal Information shall be shared with our subscribers/advertisers and you shall be deemed to have given consent to the same. 

Gapoon takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal information provided via the Services from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. We will share Personal Information only under one or more of the following circumstances: - If we have your consent or deemed consent to do so OR If we are compelled by law (including court orders) to do so. 

You acknowledge that you are disclosing Personal Information voluntarily. Prior to the completion of any registration process on our website or prior to availing of any services offered on our website if you wish not to disclose any Personal Information you may refrain from doing so; however if you don't provide information that is requested it is possible that the registration process would be incomplete and/or you would not be able to avail all of our services. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Any changes to our privacy policy will be communicated through our website and is the responsibility of the users to frequently update themselves. 

If you have questions or concerns about these privacy policies; please send us an email at contactus@gapoon.com
